kanjou ni tsukeru
I can assign whatever name I wish
namae wa jiyuu dane
To these emotions.
hora kawarihateta
See, they've already ceased to change.
kesenai boku no
The trigger of
tsumi no hikigane ga
My unrepentable sins
toketeshimaisou de
Seems ready to melt away,
nikushimi ga kieteshimattara
But if this hatefulness fades,
kimi o korosenai kara
I'll lose my chance to kill you.
kako o tannou shiteiru
I'm experiencing every moment of my past,
tsumi ga tsukutta boku ni kawaru tame ni
Trying to become the person who created these sins
ASL no naifu de
With an ASL knife.
kioku no signal kizamareteru noni
Despite the signal carved into my memories,
itami sae keshisatteshimau kizuna no spiral
Even the pain is erased away by this spiral of causality.
Having wandered in, I begin to fade... ceasing to be myself.
mayoikonda boku wa boku de kietekureteiku
Black and Deep Desires
漆黑的野心
本字幕由✿花語&千夏字幕組✿共同製作
Why'd you go after Mr. Nero?
なんで ネロさんを狙った
Who put you up to it?
誰の差金だ
How'd you know it was Corteo?
なぜ コルテオだと
He leaked Nero's schedule to Fango,
ネロさんの動きをファンゴに流していました
then came back to the Island yesterday.
昨日もアイランドに来て
Then this man came to throw himself at our mercy,
それで がコルテオの情報を手土産に
with the info about Corteo.
泣きついて来たって訳だ
The higher-ups want to work with you guys.
上は あんたらと手を組みたがってます
With Fango gone, we're done for.
ファンゴがいないと うちはもう終わりですから
Hey.
You came to us from Orco, right?
お前 オルコんとこからうちに流れて来たんだったな
Yeah. I'm Carmelo.
ええ カメロっす
Cut the half-assed crap. Move!
生温いことしてんじゃね 退け
Why'd you go after Nero?
何故 ネロを狙った
What were you and Fango planning?
ファンゴと何を企んでた
Was anyone else in on it?
他に仲間は
Say something!
なんとか言え
We don't have a choice.
どうしようもねぇ
Corteo needs to die.
コルテオには死んでもらう
Nero, got a moment?
ネロ ちょっといいか
Sure.
I've called the Fango family executives to meet with us in the morning.
明日の朝 ファンゴ ファミリーの幹部連中を呼んだ
We'll talk with them then.
話をつけよう
Got it.
分かった
And about Corteo...
それで コルテオのことだな
Could you leave us alone?
外してくれるか
The Fango, you know?
あのファンゴがね
I still can't believe it...
まだ 信じらんねよ
Hey, Avilio.
おぉ アヴィリオ
This is hard for you as well, right?
おめぇもつれぇとこだな
You've known Corteo a long time...
コルテオとは 付き合いなげぇんだろう
Has he said anything yet?
あいつ 何が話したか
Not a word.
これが何一つ喋らね
Guess it'll take more time.
まだまだ 掛かりそうだわ
But at the rate he's going,
Mr. Ganzo might just kill him.
でも あの様子だと ガンゾさんがやっちまいそうだですね
He's got a real temper when it comes to Nero.
叔父貴はネロのことになると 頭に血がのぼるからな
He might get carried away and—
勢い余っ...
Sorry.
すまね
Not at all.
いや
Avilio, it's me.
アヴィリオ 俺だ
I see... so he got caught, huh?
そうか やっぱり捕まっちまったか
There's nothin' I can do, is there?
俺に 何か出来ることねぇかな
I... He...
俺...あいつに...
What happened?
何があった
Why did Corteo kill Fango?
何故コルテオがファンゴを
Fango betrayed Corteo.
コルテオはファンゴに裏切られたんだ
Once he got the recipe from Scusa,
スクーザからレシピを手に入れたら
he said he didn't need him anymore.
もう 用済みだってよ
Never in a million years would I've seen this comin'...
まさか こんなことんなっちまうとはな
He's hated the mafia since he was a kid.
ガキの頃から ずっとマフィアを毛嫌いをしてたのに
That's irony for you. No kidding.
皮肉のもんだぜ マジで
なんであいつ
Why'd he want to kill Nero so bad that he'd team up with Fango?
ファンゴと組んでまでネロをやろうとしたんだ
You're the one who dragged me into this!
お前が巻き込んだじゃないか
H-Hey!
Hey! Someone get in here!
おい 誰か来てくれ
Damn it. That little brat...
畜生 くそがき
In back! He escaped out the window!
裏だ 窓から逃げやって
Uncle!
叔父貴
Corteo escaped!
コルテオが逃げた
Head him off!
回り込め
Hey! You okay?
大丈夫か
Ouch...
What happened?
何かあったのか
What's the meaning of this?
どういうことだ
That's what I want to know.
俺が聞きてぇぜ
This idiot just charged in out of
nowhere and whipped out a gun.
突然このバカが銃突きつけてきやがった
He got away?
逃げられた
I had a bad feeling about that guy from the start.
端から気に食わねと思っていたんだ
You trash!
くそが
Don't let him escape.
逃がすな
Right.
We've locked down all roads leading out of the city.
町から出る道は もう抑えてやる
Nero.
ネロ
About Avilio...
アヴィリオのことなんだ
He and Corteo have known each other a long time.
やつとコルテオは古い仲間だ
And he's covered for Corteo before.
それに 先もコルテオを庇うようなことを
I can't help but think—
どうも俺には...
That's because they're old friends from childhood.
それは 幼馴染みだからな
Barbero, you've got a habit of being too suspicious.
バルベロ 何でも疑い過ぎんのは お前の悪い癖だぜ
First, we find Corteo.
まずは コルテオを見つけ出す
Everything else comes after that.
ずべては そっからだ
I see... If you find him, let me know.
そうか 見つかったら教えてくれ
Right.
Corteo?
コルテオが
I'm sorry.
ごめん
They're going to kill me.
僕は殺される...
If you don't kill Nero...
...君はネロを殺さないと
Where are you now?
今どこにいる
Tomorrow...
明日
I'll call you again at this time.
またこの時間に行っています
If Nero's not dead by then, they'll kill me.
その時までにネロが死んでないと 僕の命はない
Who's with you?
誰といるんだ
The one who sent you that letter is—
あの手紙のお送り主は...
I think it was...
たしか
Lagusa. Something like that.
ラグーザとか言ったは
You weren't alone, right?
一人でじゃないような
There were four of us, including me.
おれを入れて四人だ
There was one more...
後 もう一人
Whoops.
Hey.
You're taking it easy.
呑気なもんだ
I'm not an idiot like Fango.
俺はファンゴみたいな間抜けじゃね
Any trace of Corteo?
コルテオの足取りは
Not yet.
まだつかめねえ
Some former bigwigs are meeting today to
talk about where the family goes from here.
今日 主だったのが集まってファミリーの今後について話す
With Fango out of the picture, too...
ファンゴの野郎もくたばったしなぁ
You should come.
お前も立ち会え
I will.
分かった
Uncle, how's the wound?
叔父 傷はどうだ
It hurts a bit, but it's nothing serious.
ちっとは痛むが大したことはねぇ
Any word on him?
それより あいつは
We haven't found him yet,
まだ 見つかっていません
but it's likely just a matter of time.
時間の問題でしょうかね
Sorry to call you all the way out here.
わざわざ呼び出してすまんな
Dad.
親父
I want Barbero to serve as a
family executive from now on.
バルベロには 今後ファミリーの幹部として働いてもらう
Don, I swear my loyalty to you anew.
ドン より一層の忠誠を誓います
And this is Avilio Bruno, a new recruit.
後 新しく入ったアヴィリオ ブルノ
The one with the booze?
あの酒の?
Yeah, he's the one who brought it to us.
あぁ こいつが持ち込んできた
He's got a lot of moxie.
なかなか根性が据ってる
Take care of Nero.
ネロを頼んだぞ
I will, Don.
分かりました ドン
Children grow up before you know it.
子供はいつの間にか大人になっちまう
You do so much for them and yet...
あんだけ世話をしたのに
Frate's dead and Fio's gone too.
フラテは死に フィオも去った
Nero, I'm not blaming you.
ネロ お前を責めているわけじゃない
You did it all to protect the family.
すべてはファミリーを守るためだった
I thought welcoming Ronaldo into the family was the best way to protect it,
俺はぁ ロナルドを迎え入れることがファミリーを守る道だと考えた
and I listened to Ronaldo over you.
そして お前ではなくロナルドの言葉を受け入れてきた
However that just made things worse with Frate.
だが それがフラテを増長させてしまった
In the end, Ronaldo was an outsider.
結局 ロナルドは外の人間だ
That's right. I was wrong.
そうだ 俺は間違っていた
I was trying to do everything I could for the family as our don, but...
ドンとしてファミリーにとっての最善を尽くしたつもりだったが
It all came to nothing.
なんてことはない
It was just the shallow thinking of a senile old man.
耄碌爺の浅知恵だったというわけだ
That's enough. It's all in the past now.
もういい すべて終わったことだ
If that boy...
あの子が...
If Frate hadn't died, the Galassias would never have stepped back.
フラテが死ななければ ガラッシアは黙っていなかった
Nero, you did the right thing.
ネロ お前はやるべきことをやった
"God helps those who help themselves."
自ら動かぬ者に天はその手を差し伸べず
Starting today, you sit here.
これからは お前がここに座るんだ
もうご存知かと思いますが
As I believe you know,
the Fango family is now incorporated into ours.
ファンゴ ファミリーがわれわれの傘下に入りました
よって 今後は
Thus from now on, I'd like to reconsider
the Island as a primary sales route,
アイランドを中心に 販売経路の見直し
continue rebuilding while expanding the Lodge,
再構築を進め 同時にロッジの規模を拡大
and work toward mass production.
量産にも力を入れていきます
Then, regarding Lawless Heaven,
なお ローレスヘブンについては
I'd like to prepare to sell it in Chicago in the near future.
近々 シカゴに卸す準備を始めます
Chicago? The Galassias won't like that.
シカゴ ? ガラッシアが黙ってねぞ
We'll negotiate with them, of course.
もちろん話は通す
そこでだ
To that end, I'd like to send some to Don
Galassia before the playhouse's opening.
劇場の杮落としで会う前に
前もって 酒をドン ガラッシアに届けておきたい
Avilio.
アヴィリオ
Will you go in my place?
俺の代わりに行ってきてくれ
Wait, Nero. Let me handle that.
待ってネロ それなら俺が行く
Avilio's not ready...
アヴィリオはまだ...
No, we'll leave this one to Avilio.
いや 今回はアヴィリオに任せる
俺たちには劇場の準備があるしなぁ
We have the preparations on the playhouse to finish.
Can you handle it?
やれるか
Yeah.
I'm counting on you.
頼んだぜ
Dad, rehearsals are starting at the playhouse soon.
親父 近々劇場でリハサールが始まる
Everything's in place.
万事順調だ
I see. I can't wait.
そうか 楽しみにしてるぞ
Wow, you're the don, Nero?
ネロがドンかよ
Don't worry. You'll make a great don!
大丈夫 お前ならきっとドンになれる
Who was the man standing next to your father?
親父さんの隣にいた男は誰なんだ
Huh? You mean Del Toro?
デル トロの事か?
I've never seen him speak.
喋ってるのを見たこと無い
Yeah, I hear he got messed up in the war.
大概是第一次世界大戰
前の大戦でやられたそうだ
The one in Europe. He's served
under my dad ever since fighting there.
ヨーロッパでなぁ 戦ってた時から親父の部下だった
He's quite an old-timer, then.
相当な古株だなぁ
Wasn't he in prison?
あの人は確か務所に入ってた
Yeah, on a job for the family.
ファミリーの仕事でだ
He got out...
そう で...
the year before last, I think?
一昨年だっけか 出てきたのは
How long was he in for?
どれくらい 入ってた
Not sure, five years or so, I think.
さぁな 五年かそこらだろ
He went to prison seven years ago...
務所の入ったのは七年前
Your first job... was that with him?
お前の初仕事も 一緒だったのか
いや 来ることになってたが
Nah. He was supposed to come along, but got sent to prison before then.
その前務所に入っちまった
Gotta piss.
小便だ
Tomorrow...
明日
I'll call you again at this time.
また この時間に電話する
If Nero's not dead by then, they'll kill me.
その時にネロが死んでないと 僕の命はない
Hey.
Uncle Ganzo thinks pretty highly of you.
ガンゾの叔父貴 随分お前のこと買ってるぜ
Does he?
そうなのか
He really pushed for me to take you there.
あそこにお前を連れて行くのを だいぶ押してくれた
I was shocked. He's always been an old-fashioned kinda guy.
驚いたぜ なんせ 昔気質のおじさんだからなぁ
I was sure he'd be the first to argue against it, but it was the opposite.
真っ先に反対されるかと思ったら 逆だった
I see...
そうか
I'm glad your dad acknowledged you, too.
お前こそ 認められて良かったなぁ
I'm pretty drunk. Going on ahead.
だいぶ酔った 先に帰る
Seven years ago...
七年前
That night, when Dad took me along on my first job...
親父に初めて仕事に連れて行かれたあの夜
It wasn't just the kid who ran away.
逃げたガキだけじゃねぇ
I couldn't shoot anyone.
誰も撃つことが出来なかった
I was afraid to shoot.
撃つのが怖かった
I felt like Dad held me in contempt for it.
親父に軽蔑された気がした
That's why I've thrown myself into my work to get him to acknowledge me.
だから 親父に認めてもらう為に我武者羅にやってきた
A lot of killing.
殺してきた
And then, even Frate...
そして フラテも...
In the end, maybe nothing's really changed...
結局 あの時からなん変わってねぇかもなぁ
But you could kill him now, right?
でも 今ならやれるだろう
That kid you failed to shoot
七年前は撃ち損なった
seven years ago.
そのガキを
It was you, wasn't it?
あんただったんだなぁ
Right answer, Angelo.
正解だ アンジェロ